Register of the Gerald Lee Warren papers, 1956-1994
Hoover Institution Archives
- White House Subject File, 1969-1977 (Boxes 90-217)
  - Domestic programs
    - Protest movements
      - Press briefings
        - Undated (Box-folder 149: 5)
        - 1970 April (Box-folder 149: 6)
        - 1973 January (Box-folder 149: 7)
        - 1974 September (Box-folder 149: 8)
      - Press conferences
        - Undated (Box-folder 149: 9)
        - 1969 June (Box-folder 149: 10)
        - 1970
          - March (Box-folder 149: 11)
          - May-July (Box-folder 149: 12-14)
          - September (Box-folder 149: 15)
        - 1973 August (Box-folder 149: 16)
        - 1974 September (Box-folder 149: 17)
      - Press releases
        - 1970
          - April-May (Box-folder 149: 18-19)
          - November (Box-folder 149: 20)
        - 1971
          - April-May (Box-folder 149: 21-22)
          - December (Box-folder 149: 23)
      - Proclamations
        - 1974 September (Box-folder 149: 24)
        - 1975 March (Box-folder 149: 25)
      - Remarks
        - 1970 May-June (Box-folder 149: 26-27)
        - 1971 May (Box-folder 149: 28)
      - Statements
        - Undated (Box-folder 149: 29)
          Includes typescript and draft.
        - 1970 May (Box-folder 149: 30)
        - 1971 August (Box-folder 149: 31)
        - 1974 September (Box-folder 149: 32)
      - Telegrams, 1970 April-May (Box-folder 149: 33-34)
      - Television news reports
        - 1970 May (Box-folder 149: 35)
        - 1971 May (Box-folder 149: 36)
      - Wire releases, undated (Box-folder 149: 37)
    - Science and technology
      - Fact sheets
        - Undated (Box-folder 149: 38)
        - 1970 April (Box-folder 149: 39)
        - 1972
          - March (Box-folder 149: 40)
          - October (Box-folder 149: 41)
        - 1975 June (Box-folder 149: 42)
      - Meetings
        - General (holograph) (Box-folder 149: 43)
        - 1971 March (Box-folder 149: 44)
        - 1972 January (Box-folder 149: 45)
        - 1974
          - July (Box-folder 149: 46)
          - September (Box-folder 149: 47)
        - 1975 April (Box-folder 149: 48)
      - Memoranda
        - Undated (Box-folder 149: 49)
        - 1969 July (Box-folder 149: 50)
        - 1971
          - July (Box-folder 149: 51)
          - December (Box-folder 149: 52)
        - 1972
          - January (Box-folder 149: 53)
          - April (Box-folder 149: 54)
          - December (Box-folder 149: 55)
        - 1974 July (Box-folder 149: 56)
      - Messages
        - 1972
          - March-April (Box-folder 149: 57-58)
          - December (Box-folder 149: 59)
        - 1974 March (Box-folder 149: 60)
        - 1975
          - March (Box-folder 149: 61)
          - June (Box-folder 149: 62)
      - Newsletters, 1975 August (Box-folder 149: 63)
      - News summaries, 1972 December (Box-folder 149: 64)
      - Press briefings
        - 1969 July (Box-folder 149: 65)
        - 1971 November (Box-folder 149: 66)
        - 1975 June (Box-folder 149: 67)
      - Press conferences
        - 1970
          - April-May (Box-folder 149: 68-69)
          - August (Box-folder 149: 70)
        - 1971 March (Box-folder 149: 71)
        - 1972
          - March (Box-folder 149: 72)
          - June (Box-folder 149: 73)
        - 1975 May (Box-folder 149: 74)
      - Press releases
        - 1969 November (Box-folder 149: 75)
        - 1972
          - April (Box-folder 150: 1)
          - October (Box-folder 150: 2)
        - 1973 October (Box-folder 150: 3)
        - 1975 June (Box-folder 150: 4)
      - Proclamations
        - 1970 April (Box-folder 150: 5)
        - 1971 July (Box-folder 150: 6)
      - Remarks
        - Undated (Box-folder 150: 7)
        - 1969 July (Box-folder 150: 8)
        - 1970 April (Box-folder 150: 9)
        - 1971
          - March (Box-folder 150: 10)
          - May (Box-folder 150: 11)
        - 1973 October (Box-folder 150: 12)
        - 1975 June (Box-folder 150: 13)
      - Reports
        - 1968 (Box-folder 150: 14)
          Booklet.
        - 1971 October (Box-folder 150: 15)
      - Schedules, undated (Box-folder 150: 16)
      - Statements
        - Undated (Box-folder 150: 17)
        - 1969 March (Box-folder 150: 18)
        - 1970
          - March-April (Box-folder 150: 19-20)
          - July (Box-folder 150: 21)
        - 1971
          - February (Box-folder 150: 22)
          - July (Box-folder 150: 23)
        - 1972 December (Box-folder 150: 24)
        - 1973 November (Box-folder 150: 25)
        - 1974 February (Box-folder 150: 26)
      - Telegrams
        - 1969
          - May (Box-folder 150: 27)
          - July (Box-folder 150: 28)
        - 1971 February (Box-folder 150: 29)
        - 1972 December (Box-folder 150: 30)
    - Social services
      - Correspondence
        - 1970
          - May (Box-folder 150: 31)
          - December (Box-folder 150: 32)
        - 1971
          - January-February (Box-folder 150: 33-34)
          - May-June (Box-folder 150: 35-36)
          - September (Box-folder 150: 37)
          - December (Box-folder 150: 38)
      - Executive orders, 1974 March (Box-folder 150: 39)
      - Fact sheets
        - Undated (Box-folder 150: 40)
        - 1971
          - June (Box-folder 150: 41)
          - August (Box-folder 150: 42)
          - November (Box-folder 150: 43)
        - 1972
          - March-May (Box-folder 150: 44-46)
          - July (Box-folder 150: 47)
        - 1973 March (Box-folder 150: 48)
        - 1974 March (Box-folder 150: 49)
        - 1975 May (Box-folder 150: 50)
      - Interviews
        - 1970 June (Box-folder 150: 51)
        - 1971 January (Box-folder 150: 52)
      - Meetings
        - 1971
          - February-May (Box-folder 150: 53-56)
          - July-August (Box-folder 150: 57-58)
          - November (Box-folder 150: 59)
        - 1972
          - February (Box-folder 150: 60)
          - June (Box-folder 150: 61)
        - 1974 August (Box-folder 150: 62)
      - Memoranda
        - Undated (Box-folder 150: 63)
        - 1970 November (Box-folder 150: 64)
        - 1971
          - February-June (Box-folder 150: 65-69)
          - October (Box-folder 150: 70)
        - 1972
          - March (Box-folder 150: 71)
          - June-August (Box-folder 150: 72-74)
        - 1973 February-March (Box-folder 150: 75-76)
      - Messages
        - 1971 March (Box-folder 151: 1)
        - 1972
          - March (Box-folder 151: 2)
          - May (Box-folder 151: 3)
        - 1975
          - May (Box-folder 151: 4)
          - July (Box-folder 151: 5)
      - Newsletters, general, 1975 (Box-folder 151: 6)
      - News summaries
        - 1969 September (Box-folder 151: 7)
        - 1970 November (Box-folder 151: 8)
        - 1971 January (Box-folder 151: 9)
        - 1972 August (Box-folder 151: 10)
      - Pool reports, 1974 March (Box-folder 151: 11)
      - Press briefings
        - 1971 September (Box-folder 151: 12)
        - 1972
          - January (Box-folder 151: 13)
          - August (Box-folder 151: 14)
          - October (Box-folder 151: 15)
        - 1973 September-October (Box-folder 151: 16-17)
        - 1974 March (Box-folder 151: 18)
        - 1975
          - January-February (Box-folder 151: 19-20)
          - May (Box-folder 151: 21)
      - Press conferences
        - Undated (Box-folder 151: 22)
        - 1970
          - March (Box-folder 151: 23)
          - June (Box-folder 151: 24)
          - December (Box-folder 151: 25)
        - 1971
          - March-June (Box-folder 151: 26-29)
          - November (Box-folder 151: 30)
        - 1972
          - February-March (Box-folder 151: 31-32)
          - May (Box-folder 151: 33)
          - July-October (Box-folder 151: 34-37)
        - 1973 March (Box-folder 151: 38)
        - 1974
          - February (Box-folder 151: 39)
          - May (Box-folder 151: 40)
      - Press releases
        - Undated (Box-folder 151: 41)
        - 1970 August-September (Box-folder 151: 42-43)
        - 1971
          - April (Box-folder 151: 44)
          - July (Box-folder 151: 45)
        - 1972 March (Box-folder 151: 46)
        - 1973 February (Box-folder 151: 47)
        - 1974 March (Box-folder 151: 48)
      - Printed matter, undated (Box-folder 151: 49)
      - Proclamations
        - 1970 September (Box-folder 151: 50)
        - 1971
          - April-May (Box-folder 151: 51-52)
          - September-November (Box-folder 151: 53-55)
        - 1972
          - May-June (Box-folder 151: 56-57)
          - September-November (Box-folder 151: 58-60)
        - 1973
          - March (Box-folder 151: 61)
          - September-October (Box-folder 151: 62-63)
        - 1974
          - May (Box-folder 151: 64)
          - July (Box-folder 151: 65)
      - Remarks
        - 1970
          - March (Box-folder 152: 1)
          - July (Box-folder 152: 2)
          - December (Box-folder 152: 3)
        - 1971
          - June (Box-folder 152: 4)
          - December (Box-folder 152: 5)
        - 1972
          - January (Box-folder 152: 6)
          - October (Box-folder 152: 7)
        - 1973 October (Box-folder 152: 8)
        - 1975 May-July (Box-folder 152: 9-11)
      - Reports, 1970 September (Box-folder 152: 12)
      - Schedules, 1972, January (Box-folder 152: 13)
      - Statements
        - Undated (Box-folder 152: 14)
        - 1969 April (Box-folder 152: 15)
        - 1970
          - March-June (Box-folder 152: 16-19)
          - October (Box-folder 152: 20)
        - 1971
          - January-February (Box-folder 152: 21-22)
          - April-June (Box-folder 152: 23-25)
          - November (Box-folder 152: 26)
        - 1972
          - January-February (Box-folder 152: 27-28)
          - May (Box-folder 152: 29)
          - August-September (Box-folder 152: 30-31)
          - December (Box-folder 152: 32)
        - 1973
          - March (Box-folder 152: 33)
          - July (Box-folder 152: 34)
        - 1974
          - June (Box-folder 152: 35)
          - October (Box-folder 152: 36)
        - 1975 February (Box-folder 152: 37)
      - Telegrams, 1972 October (Box-folder 152: 38)
      - Television news reports
        - Undated (Box-folder 152: 39)
        - 1971 January (Box-folder 152: 40)
      - Testimonies, 1969 September (Box-folder 152: 41)
    - Terrorism
      - Correspondence
        - 1970 October (Box-folder 152: 42)
        - 1972
          - June (Box-folder 152: 43)
          - August (Box-folder 152: 44)
      - Fact sheets, 1973 March (Box-folder 152: 45)
      - Memoranda
        - 1970 September (Box-folder 152: 46)
        - 1972
          - June (Box-folder 152: 47)
          - September (Box-folder 152: 48)
          - November (Box-folder 152: 49)
      - Messages, 1971 April (Box-folder 152: 50)
      - News summaries, 1972 September (Box-folder 152: 51)
      - Press briefings
        - 1972
          - June (Box-folder 152: 52)
          - September (Box-folder 152: 53)
          - November (Box-folder 152: 54)
        - 1975 July (Box-folder 152: 55)
      - Press conferences, 1970 September (Box-folder 152: 56)
      - Press releases, 1972 September (Box-folder 152: 57)
      - Remarks, 1972
        - June (Box-folder 152: 58)
        - September (Box-folder 152: 59)
      - Statements
        - Undated (Box-folder 152: 60)
        - 1970 September (Box-folder 152: 61)
        - 1972
          - March (Box-folder 152: 62)
          - June (Box-folder 152: 63)
          - November (Box-folder 152: 64)
        - 1975 March (Box-folder 152: 65)
      - Telegrams
        - 1970 March (Box-folder 152: 66)
        - 1972
          - June (Box-folder 152: 67)
          - September (Box-folder 152: 68)
    - Tourism
      - Fact sheets, 1975 July (Box-folder 152: 69)
      - Messages, 1973 September (Box-folder 152: 70)
      - Press releases, 1974 September (Box-folder 152: 71)
      - Remarks, 1975 July (Box-folder 152: 72)
    - Transportation
      - Correspondence
        - Undated (Box-folder 153: 1)
        - 1970
          - June (Box-folder 153: 2)
          - August-October (Box-folder 153: 3-5)
        - 1971 July (Box-folder 153: 6)
        - 1972 April (Box-folder 153: 7)
      - Executive orders, undated (Box-folder 153: 8)
      - Fact sheets
        - Undated (Box-folder 153: 9)
        - 1970 December (Box-folder 153: 10)
        - 1971
          - March (Box-folder 153: 11)
          - May (Box-folder 153: 12)
        - 1972 January (Box-folder 153: 13)
        - 1973 August (Box-folder 153: 14)
        - 1974 February (Box-folder 153: 15)
        - 1975
          - May (Box-folder 153: 16)
          - July (Box-folder 153: 17)
      - Meetings
        - 1971 March (Box-folder 153: 18)
        - 1974 September (Box-folder 153: 19)
        - 1975 June (Box-folder 153: 20)
      - Memoranda
        - Undated (Box-folder 153: 21)
        - 1969 July (Box-folder 153: 22)
        - 1971 March (Box-folder 153: 23)
        - 1972
          - March-April (Box-folder 153: 24-25)
          - October (Box-folder 153: 26)
        - 1974 June (Box-folder 153: 27)
        - 1975 May-June (Box-folder 153: 28-29)
      - Messages
        - 1971 September (Box-folder 153: 30)
        - 1974 February (Box-folder 153: 31)
        - 1975
          - May (Box-folder 153: 32)
          - July (Box-folder 153: 33)
      - News summaries
        - Undated (Box-folder 153: 34)
        - 1970 September (Box-folder 153: 35)
      - Press briefings
        - 1971
          - May (Box-folder 153: 36)
          - August (Box-folder 153: 37)
          - October (Box-folder 153: 38)
        - 1972 September (Box-folder 153: 39)
        - 1973 June (Box-folder 153: 40)
        - 1974
          - January (Box-folder 153: 41)
          - September (Box-folder 153: 42)
          - November (Box-folder 153: 43)
        - 1975
          - February (Box-folder 153: 44)
          - April-July (Box-folder 153: 45-48)
      - Press conferences
        - Undated (Box-folder 153: 49)
        - 1970
          - March (Box-folder 153: 50)
          - June (Box-folder 153: 51)
        - 1971
          - March (Box-folder 153: 52)
          - May (Box-folder 153: 53)
        - 1972
          - March (Box-folder 153: 54)
          - June (Box-folder 153: 55)
        - 1973 August (Box-folder 153: 56)
        - 1974 February (Box-folder 153: 57)
        - 1975 May-June (Box-folder 153: 58-59)
      - Press releases
        - 1970 December (Box-folder 153: 60)
        - 1971 March (Box-folder 153: 61)
        - 1973 August (Box-folder 153: 62)
      - Proclamations
        - 1970 March (Box-folder 153: 63)
        - 1971 August (Box-folder 153: 64)
        - 1972 September (Box-folder 153: 65)
        - 1973
          - March (Box-folder 153: 66)
          - September (Box-folder 153: 67)
        - 1974 May (Box-folder 153: 68)
        - 1975 April (Box-folder 153: 69)
      - Remarks
        - 1969 September (Box-folder 154: 1)
        - 1970 October (Box-folder 154: 2)
        - 1971 March (Box-folder 154: 3)
          Telephone conversation.
        - 1974 February (Box-folder 154: 4)
        - 1975 March-April (Box-folder 154: 5-6)
      - Schedules, 1971 March (Box-folder 154: 7)
      - Statements
        - Undated (Box-folder 154: 8)
        - 1969 December (Box-folder 154: 9)
        - 1970
          - June (Box-folder 154: 10)
          - December (Box-folder 154: 11)
        - 1971
          - March (Box-folder 154: 12)
          - May (Box-folder 154: 13)
        - 1973 August (Box-folder 154: 14)
      - Telegrams, 1970 March (Box-folder 154: 15)
    - United States Information Agency
      - Executive orders, 1970 April (Box-folder 154: 16)
      - Interviews, 1972 May (Box-folder 154: 17)
      - Messages, 1973 July (Box-folder 154: 18)
    - United States Information Services, correspondence, 1973 February (Box-folder 154: 19)
    - Veterans' affairs
      - Correspondence
        - 1971 June (Box-folder 154: 20)
        - 1972 May (Box-folder 154: 21)
      - Executive orders
        - 1971 June (Box-folder 154: 22)
        - 1973 January (Box-folder 154: 23)
      - Fact sheets
        - 1972 May (Box-folder 154: 24)
        - 1973 October (Box-folder 154: 25)
        - 1974
          - General (Box-folder 154: 26)
          - January (Box-folder 154: 27)
          - March (Box-folder 154: 28)
          - May (Box-folder 154: 29)
      - Meetings
        - 1971 June (Box-folder 154: 30)
        - 1974 April-May (Box-folder 154: 31-32)
      - Memoranda
        - Undated (Box-folder 154: 33)
        - 1971 August (Box-folder 154: 34)
        - 1972
          - April (Box-folder 154: 35)
          - October (Box-folder 154: 36)
        - 1973
          - March (Box-folder 154: 37)
          - December (Box-folder 154: 38)
        - 1974
          - January (Box-folder 154: 39)
          - March-April (Box-folder 154: 40-41)
      - Messages
        - Undated (Box-folder 154: 42)
        - 1971 May (Box-folder 154: 43)
        - 1974 January (Box-folder 154: 44)
      - Pool reports, undated (Box-folder 154: 45)
      - Press briefings
        - Undated (Box-folder 154: 46)
        - 1970 March (Box-folder 154: 47)
        - 1971
          - June (Box-folder 154: 48)
          - September (Box-folder 154: 49)
        - 1974 April-May (Box-folder 154: 50-51)
        - 1975
          - January (Box-folder 154: 52)
          - April (Box-folder 154: 53)
      - Press conferences
        - 1970
          - April-May (Box-folder 154: 54-55)
          - October-November (Box-folder 154: 56-57)
        - 1971
          - April (Box-folder 154: 58)
          - June (Box-folder 154: 59)
        - 1972 May (Box-folder 154: 60)
        - 1974 April (Box-folder 154: 61)
      - Press releases
        - 1971 June (Box-folder 154: 62)
        - 1972 May (Box-folder 154: 63)
        - 1973 December (Box-folder 154: 64)
      - Proclamations
        - 1970 September (Box-folder 154: 65)
        - 1971 September (Box-folder 154: 66)
        - 1975 May (Box-folder 154: 67)
      - Remarks
        - Undated (Box-folder 154: 68)
        - 1970
          - March (Box-folder 154: 69)
          - August (Box-folder 154: 70)
          - November (Box-folder 154: 71)
        - 1971 October (Box-folder 154: 72)
        - 1972
          - March (Box-folder 154: 73)
          - October (Box-folder 154: 74)
        - 1973
          - February (Box-folder 154: 75)
          - March (Box-folder 155: 1)
        - 1974 February-March (Box-folder 155: 2-3)
        - 1975 June (Box-folder 155: 4)
      - Reports
        - Undated (Box-folder 155: 5)
        - 1973 March (Box-folder 155: 6)
      - Statements
        - 1970 April (Box-folder 155: 7)
        - 1971 April (Box-folder 155: 8)
        - 1974 April-May (Box-folder 155: 9-10)
        - 1975 May (Box-folder 155: 11)
      - Telegrams
        - 1971 April (Box-folder 155: 12)
        - 1972 October (Box-folder 155: 13)
        - 1973 December (Box-folder 155: 14)
    - Vocational rehabilitation
      - Fact sheets
        - Undated (Box-folder 155: 15)
        - 1973
          - March (Box-folder 155: 16)
          - September (Box-folder 155: 17)
      - Meetings, 1972 July (Box-folder 155: 18)
      - Memoranda, 1974 May (Box-folder 155: 19)
      - Press conferences, 1973
        - March (Box-folder 155: 20)
        - September (Box-folder 155: 21)
      - Press releases, 1973 September (Box-folder 155: 22)
      - Schedules, 1970 November (Box-folder 155: 23)
      - Statements, 1973 September (Box-folder 155: 24)
    - Volunteerism
      - Correspondence, 1970 July (Box-folder 155: 25)
      - Executive orders, 1974 January (Box-folder 155: 26)
      - Fact sheets
        - 1971 March (Box-folder 155: 27)
        - 1973 October (Box-folder 155: 28)
      - Meetings, 1971
        - February (Box-folder 155: 29)
        - April (Box-folder 155: 30)
      - Memoranda
        - Undated (Box-folder 155: 31)
        - 1971 January (Box-folder 155: 32)
      - Messages, 1971 March (Box-folder 155: 33)
      - Newsletters, 1969 July (Box-folder 155: 34)
      - Press briefings, 1975 April (Box-folder 155: 35)
      - Press conferences, 1971
        - March (Box-folder 155: 36)
        - July (Box-folder 155: 37)
      - Press releases, 1973 October (Box-folder 155: 38)
      - Proclamations
        - 1970 March (Box-folder 155: 39)
        - 1971 March (Box-folder 155: 40)
        - 1974 April (Box-folder 155: 41)
      - Remarks
        - 1970 July (Box-folder 155: 42)
        - 1975 May (Box-folder 155: 43)
      - Statements
        - 1969 April (Box-folder 155: 44)
        - 1970 July (Box-folder 155: 45)
        - 1971
          - January (Box-folder 155: 46)
          - March (Box-folder 155: 47)
        - 1973 May (Box-folder 155: 48)
  - Foreign policy
    - Correspondence, 1972 October (Box-folder 155: 49)
    - Fact sheets
      - Undated (Box-folder 155: 50)
      - 1969 July (Box-folder 155: 51)
      - 1971-1972 (Box-folder 155: 52-53)
    - Interviews
      - Undated (Box-folder 155: 54)
      - 1969 December (Box-folder 155: 55)
      - 1970 July (Box-folder 155: 56)
      - 1971 October (Box-folder 155: 57)
      - 1972
        - May (Box-folder 155: 58)
        - September (Box-folder 155: 59)
      - 1973 July (Box-folder 155: 60)
      - 1974 June (Box-folder 155: 61)
      - 1975 May (Box-folder 155: 62)
    - Meetings
      - 1971
        - March (Box-folder 156: 1)
        - July (Box-folder 156: 2)
      - 1973 January (Box-folder 156: 3)
      - 1974
        - August (Box-folder 156: 4)
        - November (Box-folder 156: 5)
    - Memoranda
      - Undated (Box-folder 156: 6)
      - 1970 June (Box-folder 156: 7)
      - 1972
        - March (Box-folder 156: 8)
        - August (Box-folder 156: 9)
      - 1973
        - April (Box-folder 156: 10)
        - September (Box-folder 156: 11)
    - Newsletters
      - 1970 November (Box-folder 156: 12)
      - 1972 November (Box-folder 156: 13)
      - 1973 September (Box-folder 156: 14)
      - 1975 June-July (Box-folder 156: 15-16)
    - News summaries
      - 1969 July (Box-folder 156: 17)
      - 1970
        - July (Box-folder 156: 18)
        - November-December (Box-folder 156: 19-20)
      - 1971 March (Box-folder 156: 21)
      - 1973 February (Box-folder 156: 22)
    - Pool reports
      - Undated (Box-folder 156: 23)
      - 1973
        - February (Box-folder 156: 24)
        - June (Box-folder 156: 25)
    - Press briefings
      - Undated (Box-folder 156: 26)
      - 1969
        - February (Box-folder 156: 27)
        - July (Box-folder 156: 28)
        - November-December (Box-folder 156: 29-30)
      - 1970
        - January-June (Box-folder 156: 31-36)
        - July-October (Box-folder 157: 1-4)
        - December (Box-folder 157: 5)
      - 1971 (Box-folder 157: 6-17)
      - 1972
        - January-April (Box-folder 157: 18-21)
        - May-December (Box-folder 158: 1-8)
      - 1973
        - February-March (Box-folder 158: 9-10)
        - June-December (Box-folder 158: 11-17)
      - 1974
        - January-February (Box-folder 158: 18-19)
        - April-May (Box-folder 158: 20-21)
        - June-December (Box-folder 159: 1-7)
      - 1975 January-June (Box-folder 159: 8-13)
    - Press conferences
      - Undated (Box-folder 159: 14)
      - 1969
        - February-April (Box-folder 159: 15-17)
        - June (Box-folder 159: 18)
        - November (Box-folder 159: 19)
      - 1970
        - April (Box-folder 159: 20)
        - July (Box-folder 159: 21)
        - October-November (Box-folder 159: 22-23)
      - 1971
        - March-April (Box-folder 159: 24-25)
        - June (Box-folder 160: 1)
        - August (Box-folder 160: 2)
        - October-December (Box-folder 160: 3-5)
      - 1972
        - March-April (Box-folder 160: 6-7)
        - June (Box-folder 160: 8)
      - 1973